socialmoov.com 2014-06-25

# Tracking privacy policy social moov | Social Moov

## Tracking Privacy Policy – SOCIAL MOOV

**Tracking through Social Moov Technology**

Social Moov firmly believes in the importance of online privacy. Social Moov innovative social tracking and services are used to monitor and manage advertising campaigns on social networks.

**Data Collection through Social Moov Social Tracking**

Social Moov’s technology may employ cookies to collect non-personally identifying information, such as information related to advertising campaign results, in the course of providing its clients with its ad-serving services.

A cookie is a small text file that can be stored on your computer when that computer’s browser views one of Social Moov’s client’s advertisements or websites. The cookie does not contain your name, address, phone number, email address, or anything that personally identifies you. Social Moov collects into the cookie only non-personally identifying information such as the computer’s IP address, type of the computer’s operating system, type of internet browser software, what web pages were viewed and at what time, geographic location of a consumer’s internet service provider.

**Links to Other Sites**

Our site may contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different from ours. In addition, there may be links to other sites provided within the body of advertisements on other websites. We do not have control over the information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. You should consult the privacy policy of these other sites to learn how your privacy is protected.

**Data Security and Retention**

Social Moov retains anonymous log file data for up to thirteen months, following which the data is deleted.  
Social Moov is a member of the Internet Advertising Bureau (IAB) and complies with all applicable laws and regulations as well as with IAB principles as described in the **[Online Behavioural Advertising (OBA) Framework](http://www.iabeurope.eu/public-affairs/oba-framework.aspx)**.

**Optout**

Users can choose to opt out of Social Moov’s anonymous data collection program. Once users opt out, Social Moov does not collect navigation data or create marketing profiles anymore. Opting out does no prevent users from receiving online ads delivered by Social Moov, but these ads are delivered randomly. They are not targeted to a user’s modelled interest or demographics, are not delivered in sequence or delivered according to any previous advertising interaction.

When users opt out, Social Moov stores a specific cookie on their browser. Social Moov’s opt-out cookie has to be downloaded on each computer and each browser used by users. If cookies are disabled, erased, or altered, and if browsers or operating systems are modified or upgraded, the opt-out process might need to be performed again.

To perform an optout : follow this link

**Changes to this Document**

Social Moov reserves the right to change, modify, add or remove portions of this policy at any time and without notice. If we change our privacy policy, we will make every effort to post those changes in this area so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**If You Have Questions About This Policy**

To address any questions, comments, or concerns related to our privacy policy, please contact our customer support : support@socialmoov.com – Social Moov SAS, 78 rue du faubourg st antoine 75012 Paris

_Version 1.2 – Last updated Novembre 22, 2012._

**RESOURCES (click to learn more)**
